[♪♪]
I'm Peppa Pig.
This is my little brother,
George.
[SNORTS]
This is Mommy Pig.
And this is Daddy Pig.
[SNORTS]
[ALL LAUGH]
Peppa Pig.
[GRUNTS]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
It is teatime.
And Mommy Pig has a surprise
for everyone.
[SNORTS]
Today is a day for pancakes.
Pancakes. Delicious.
[GIGGLES AND SNORTS]
I love pancakes.
[LAUGHS]
[SNORTS]
[ALL LAUGH]
Everyone loves pancakes.
I'm the expert at flipping
the pancakes over.
Leave that to me.
Are you sure,
Daddy Pig?
Last time you got
a bit grumpy
when you dropped the pancake
on the floor.
I did not get grumpy.
There was a problem
with the frying pan.
[ALL LAUGH]
Mommy, can we help
make the pancakes? Please?
[SNORTS]
Yes.
You can help me
make the batter.
First I put some flour
in the bowl.
BOTH:
Ooh.
MOMMY PIG:
Now I add an egg.
Now the milk.
And I give it all
a stir.
[SNORTS]
Mommy, can I stir?
Yes, of course, Peppa.
Peppa loves stirring.
[SNORTS]
George wants to stir
as well.
[SNICKERS]
No, George, like this.
[BOTH LAUGH]
Okay, that's enough
stirring.
You two sit at the table
while I cook the pancakes.
[GAS HISSES]
[SIZZLING]
Mommy Pig is going
to flip the pancake over.
Hooray!
[ALL LAUGH]
You could flip it higher,
Mommy Pig.
You can show us how
when you flip your own pancake,
Daddy Pig.
This first pancake
is for George.
Mommy Pig pours a little syrup
on George's pancake.
[SMACKS LIPS AND SNORTS]
Delicious.
This pancake is for Peppa.
PEPPA:
Hooray!
[ALL CHUCKLE]
Hmm. You could flip it higher,
Mommy Pig.
MOMMY PIG:
You will get a chance to show me
when you flip you own pancake,
Daddy Pig.
Syrup, please.
[LIPS SMACK]
Mmm, delicious.
[LAUGHS]
This pancake
is for Mommy Pig.
PEPPA:
Hooray!
[ALL LAUGH]
You still aren't flipping them
high enough, Mommy Pig.
The next pancake is yours,
Daddy Pig.
So now you can show us
how it should be done.
[SMACKS LIPS]
Delicious.
[LAUGHS AND SNORTS]
Is everyone watching?
The secret of making
a good pancake
is to flip it high
into the air.
One, two, three...
hoopla!
[MOMMY PIG GASPS]
[GIGGLES]
Silly Daddy.
Oh.
Maybe that was just
a bit too high.
Oh, what a shame.
That was the last pancake.
It should be a simple matter
to get it down.
Oh, dear. Daddy Pig cannot
reach his pancake.
MOMMY PIG:
Don't worry, Daddy Pig.
I think I know a way
to get it down.
Let's go upstairs,
children.
[GIGGLING]
This way.
What is Mommy Pig
planning to do?
On the count of three,
we all have to start jumping
up and down.
One, two, three.
Jump!
[ALL LAUGH]
[THUDDING]
What are they doing?
[♪♪]
It worked.
Now Daddy Pig
has his pancake.
Daddy has a pancake
on his head.
[ALL LAUGH]
Hmm.
Syrup on your pancake,
Daddy Pig?
Yes, please.
[GIGGLING]
One, two, three...
hoopla!
Mmm.
Delicious.
[ALL LAUGH]
Silly Daddy.
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
Mommy Pig and Daddy Pig
are going out for the evening.
Granny Pig and Grandpa Pig
are going to babysit.
Granny Pig! Grandpa Pig!
[MISPRONOUNCES]
Hello, my little ones.
Hello.
Peppa, George,
into your beds, quick.
[BOTH GIGGLE]
Good night,
my little piggies.
Good night. Sleep tight.
Good night, Mommy.
Good night, Daddy.
[SNORTS]
What little darlings.
Now go to sleep
quickly.
Yes, Mommy.
So well-behaved.
Mommy Pig and Daddy Pig are
leaving for their evening out.
[ENGINE STARTS]
Peppa and George
are so good.
They just fell asleep
when Mommy Pig told them to.
[SNORTS]
This babysitting is easy.
George? George?
Are you awake?
[SNORTS]
[GIGGLES]
Shh!
[BOTH SNICKER]
[LOUD THUMPING]
What strange noises.
I wonder if we should
check upstairs.
[BOTH LAUGHING
AND SNORTING]
Peppa, George.
Are you awake?
Well, I never.
Fast asleep.
So it wasn't Peppa and George
making all that noise.
[SNORTS]
I can't hear anything.
I think they really have
fallen asleep.
[SNORTS]
Let's watch some television.
MAN [OVER TV]:
Gardening.
Today, we are talking
about roses.
Oh, I love gardening
programs.
The Kiftsgate is a particularly
thorny rose.
To prune it,
start by lopping off
the head
and then snip away
the budding shoots.
Granny Pig?
GRANNY PIG:
Peppa? George?
You should be
in bed asleep.
George and I
aren't sleepy at all.
[SNORTS]
Can we watch TV with you?
Well, I suppose
watching a little TV
might make you sleepy.
Hooray!
[GIGGLES]
Icelandic Roses
are a rare treat
for the discerning
horticulturist,
but they are prone to lobbing
in temperate habitats.
[YAWNS]
This program
is very boring.
[YAWNS]
Grandpa Pig,
can you play that game
where you throw us up
and catch us?
Okay, but just one turn each.
[GIGGLES]
Whee!
[LAUGHS]
Oh, you seem heavier
than before.
[SNORTING]
[LAUGHS]
Now it's George's turn.
Whee!
[BOTH LAUGH]
My turn.
Whee!
Whew.
Higher, higher.
[PANTING]
Whee!
Maybe Grandpa Pig
is a bit tired.
I know. Granny Pig,
let's play catch.
Uh...
[GIGGLES]
You're it.
Catch us if you can.
[LAUGHS]
PEPPA:
Can't catch me.
GRANNY PIG:
I'm going to catch you.
[ALL LAUGHING]
NARRATOR:
Mommy Pig and Daddy Pig
are back home.
I hope our little piggies
are asleep.
[TELEVISION STATIC CRACKLING]
Hello? Anyone here?
[ALL SNORING]
[DADDY PIG LAUGHS]
The little piggies
are asleep.
And so are
the big piggies.
[BOTH LAUGH]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
Peppa is going to her first
ballet lesson.
This is Madame Gazelle,
the ballet teacher.
Oh, you must be
young Peppa.
I am Madame Gazelle.
Hello, Madame.
Aww, so sweet.
Welcome to your first lesson
of the ballet.
[GIGGLES]
I'll pick you up later.
Bye-bye.
Enjoy yourself.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Here are Peppa's friends,
Candy Cat, Suzy Sheep,
Danny Dog,
Rebecca Rabbit
and Pedro Pony.
Children, today we have
a new pupil: Peppa Pig.
Now, Peppa, run and join
your friends.
[SNORTS AND LAUGHS]
Hello, everyone.
ALL: Hello, Peppa.
[ALL MAKING ANIMAL NOISES]
GAZELLE:
Children.
We begin with demi-plié.
[LOW-TEMPO PIANO MUSIC PLAYS]
Demi-plié.
Now a little jump.
Petit jeté.
With grace and beauty.
Grace and beauty.
Petit jeté.
[GIGGLES]
The ballet lesson
is a lot of fun.
Raise you arms.
Imagine that you are
beautiful swans.
And what noise do you think
a swan might make?
[ALL MAKING ANIMAL SOUNDS]
Oh!
[ALL CHATTER]
Grace and beauty.
Peppa loves dancing.
Everyone loves dancing.
[TOLLING]
[CHILDREN LAUGHING]
Mommy. Mommy.
[SNORTS]
We all danced as swans.
Peppa did very well.
I had to dance beautifully
and gracefully.
That's lovely.
Can I show you
how I did it?
Let's get home first.
Then you can show Daddy Pig
and George and me.
[ENGINE STARTS]
Bye-bye.
[CAR HORN BLARES]
Peppa and Mommy Pig are home.
Daddy. George.
I'm going to show you
how to do ballet.
Is it difficult?
It was easy for me.
But you, George and Mommy
will find it very hard.
[SNORTS]
First, we need music.
[GENTLE PIANO MUSIC PLAYS]
Good. Now, George,
Daddy and Mommy,
you must copy
what I do.
Madame Gazelle
used funny words.
But really it's just bending
your knees and jumping.
Ah.
The petit jeté.
Daddy! You know the funny words.
[LAUGHS]
Mommy Pig and I
used to be quite good
at ballet.
Do be careful,
Daddy Pig.
[LAUGHS AND SNORTS]
Our favorite was
the pas de deux.
Hoopla!
Oof!
Aah!
That wasn't quite
how I remembered it.
[SNICKERS]
Silly Daddy Pig.
Maybe we should leave the ballet
to Peppa.
Yes, I am the best at it.
I am a beautiful swan.
[SNORTS]
[ALL LAUGH]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
[BOTH GIGGLING]
NARRATOR:
It is a lovely, sunny day.
Peppa and George
are having a picnic.
Here's some orange juice
for you, Teddy.
What do you say?
Thank you very much,
Peppa.
You are very
welcome, Teddy.
Here's some orange juice
for you, Mr. Dinosaur.
And what do you say?
Grr!
You are very welcome,
Mr. Dinosaur.
[LAUGHS AND SNORTS]
Would Teddy or Mr. Dinosaur
like a cookie?
We're not very hungry.
So Peppa and George can eat
all the cookies.
Thank you, Teddy.
[BOTH LAUGH]
[THUNDER RUMBLES]
What is that
strange noise?
Peppa! George!
Quick, come inside
the house.
Mommy, there was
a loud bang sound.
It's thunder, Peppa.
It means there will be a
thunderstorm with lots of rain.
Quick. Into the house
before the rain starts.
[LAUGHS]
No need to panic.
The rain is still
a long way off.
The sky is getting
darker and darker.
There is going
to be a thunderstorm.
Peppa, George,
did you bring all your toys
in from the garden?
Dinosaur.
MOMMY PIG:
Good, Mr. Dinosaur is safe.
Teddy! I left Teddy
in the garden.
He'll get wet.
DADDY PIG:
Don't worry, Peppa.
Daddy Pig will rescue Teddy.
You'd better hurry, Daddy Pig.
It's just about to rain.
I know all about
thunderstorms.
It won't rain for ages.
[CHUCKLES AND SNORTS]
As I thought.
Plenty of time
before it rains.
[SHUDDERING]
[PANTING]
Poor Teddy.
He's soaking wet.
Yes, poor Teddy.
Let's get him dry.
Poor Teddy.
[SHIVERING]
There you are, Teddy.
All dry.
[BOTH LAUGH]
[SNEEZES]
What about poor Daddy?
I'm soaking wet too.
Oh. Sorry, Daddy Pig.
Let's get you dry.
[ALL LAUGH]
There you are,
Daddy Pig.
Nice and dry.
[SNORTS]
Hmm.
Oh!
The rain is coming
in the house.
The floor is getting wet.
Oh, dear.
What can we do,
Daddy Pig?
Don't worry.
Daddy Pig is using a bucket
to catch the drips.
MOMMY PIG:
Well done, Daddy Pig.
Easy as pie.
Eh? What?
[GASPS]
Quick, find something else
to catch the water.
Well done, Peppa.
Easy as pie.
[ALL LAUGH]
[THUNDER CRASHES]
Aah! Mommy, the thunder bangs
are very loud.
It's okay, children.
Don't be frightened.
Let's count between
each flash and bang.
The higher
we can count,
the further away
the thunderstorm is.
One, two, three...
[THUNDER CRASHES]
[SNORTS]
That's three.
ALL:
One, two, three,
four, five...
[THUNDER CRASHES]
That's five.
The thunderstorm
is going away.
[BIRDS SINGING]
[SNORTS]
The thunderstorm is over.
ALL:
Hooray!
The thunderstorm has filled
the garden with muddy puddles.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
Peppa loves jumping
up and down in muddy puddles.
[ALL LAUGH]
Everyone loves jumping
up and down in muddy puddles.
I love thunderstorms.
They make muddy puddles.
Splish-splash,
splosh-splish.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[PEPPA GIGGLING]
♪ Peppa Pig ♪
[SNORTS AND LAUGHS]